roningallery.com 2019-08-11

# Privacy Policy | Ronin Gallery

**Last Updated** : March 22, 2019 ****

Protecting your privacy is very important to Ronin Gallery. We have adopted the following policies to safeguard your personal data. We will limit the collection and use of your personal data to what is necessary to administer our business, provide you with the highest quality service, and offer you opportunities we think will be of interest.  

Ronin Gallery LLC ("us", "we", or "our") operates the www.RoninGallery.com website (the "Service"). This Privacy Policy describes how we may collect, use, disclose, and process your personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. With respect to the personal data of European Economic Area (EEA) data subjects, Ronin Gallery is a data controller with respect to personal data it collects through the Service.

By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined herein, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

##  **PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION**

We may collect and process the following personal data about you:

  *  **Contact Data**. You may provide us with your contact details, such as name, email address, phone number, address, state, province, ZIP/Postal code, city, or other similar information, which we may use to respond to your [inquiries](https://www.roningallery.com/contacts) or to your [requests to schedule a curated session](https://www.roningallery.com/schedule), to send you informational emails, newsletters and updates, or for administrative purposes.
  *  **Online Portal**. If you register for an account on our online portal, we may collect your name, email address, password, and other similar information.
  *  **Order Information**. If you purchase a good from the Service, you may provide us with your name, email address, order information, payment information, or other similar information.
  *  **Log Data**. We may collect information on how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers, and other diagnostic data.
  *  **Device Information**. We may obtain information about the devices that access the Service, including the type of device, its operating system, device settings, and unique device identifiers.
  *  **Other information you provide to us**. This includes emails and other communications that you send to us or otherwise contribute, such as support inquiries.

[We may also collect personal data about you from other sources, including service providers and third-party services. Such data will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.]

##  **PERSONAL DATA PROCESSING**

We process your personal data:

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To deliver the goods you purchase and process your payments
  * To schedule a curated session with you
  * To allow you access to the online portal
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To respond to your emails, inquiries, comments, questions, or other requests for customer support
  * To provide you with newsletters, special offers and general information about goods, services, and events we offer
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent, and address technical issues
  * To comply with applicable laws, regulations, or legal processes
  * To protect our or others’ interests, rights, and property

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, these processing activities are carried out pursuant to the following legal bases under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):

  * The processing is necessary for us to provide you with the goods or services you request, including pursuant to a contract with you
  * If you have consented to the use of your personal data. When you consent, you can change your mind at any time.
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it is not overridden by your rights. For example, we have a legitimate interest in the following cases:
  * To maintain and improve the Service.
  * To operate the Service and provide you with certain tailored advertising and communications to develop and promote our business.
  * To maintain business relationships using company contact information.
  * We have a legal obligation to process your personal data, such as to comply with applicable tax and other government regulations or to comply with a court order or binding law enforcement request.

##  **DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA**

We may share your personal data:

  * With our consultants, vendors, and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, such as to help provide services to you or to analyze and improve the Service.
  * If required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Ronin Gallery LLC.
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service.
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public.
  * During negotiations of any proposed or actual transaction, such as a partnership or joint venture, or any other type of legal event.

##  **COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

On the Service, we utilize online identification technologies–such as cookies, web beacons, or pixels–in accordance with applicable law and requirements. Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive when you visit a website; they store information which is sent back to our servers or those of third parties. As described in more detail below, we use such technologies to:

  * Recognize new or past visitors to the Service;
  * Store your password if you are registered on the Service;
  * Improve the Service and better understand your visits;
  * Integrate with third-party social media websites;
  * Serve you interest-based or targeted advertising; and
  * Observe your behaviors and browsing activities over time across multiple websites or other platforms.

Some cookies are required for certain uses of the Service. For example, if you choose to register an account for our Service, we will use cookies to facilitate your registration and remember your preferences.  Further details concerning the cookies we use on the Service are available in our Cookie Policy.

Browser settings may enable visitors either to receive our cookies or use the Service without cookie functionality. Please note that if you restrict the use of cookies, some functions of the Service may be unavailable. We may link the information collection by cookies with other personal data we collect from you pursuant to this Privacy Policy.

##  **SOCIAL FEATURES, ADVERTISING AND ANALYTICS**

Certain functionalities on the Service permit interactions that you initiate between the Service and third-party services, such as social networks (“Social Features”). Social Features enable you to send content between the Service and a third-party service. If you use Social Features, and potentially other third-party services, information you post or provide access to may be publicly displayed by the third-party service you use. Also, both Ronin Gallery and the third party may have access to certain information about you and your use of the Service and the third-party service.

We may use Google Analytics or other third-party service providers for analytics services. These analytics services may use cookies and other tracking technologies to analyze Service users and how they use the Service. Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

We may use remarketing services, such as Google AdWords and Facebook, to advertise on third-party websites after you visit our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service. These ads may be tailored to your interest based on your use of the Service and elsewhere on the internet, sometimes referred to as “interest-based advertising” and “online behavioral advertising,” which may include sending you an ad on a third-party service after you have left the Service (i.e., “retargeting”). Additionally, we may use your personal data to identify other individuals with similar interests and serve these individuals advertisements using services such as Facebook Lookalike Audiences.

##  **DATA SECURITY**

We maintain appropriate technical and organizational safeguards designed to help protect personal data from unauthorized disclosure or access and accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, or alteration. The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Although we use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal data obtained through the Service.

##  **RETENTION OF DATA**

We will retain your personal data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your personal data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. To determine the appropriate retention period, we will consider the amount, nature and sensitivity of the data; the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data; the purposes for which we process the data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means; and other applicable legal requirements.

##  **TRANSFER OF DATA**

If you are visiting the Services from outside of the United States, please be aware that the Ronin Gallery is based in the U.S. and the personal data that we obtain through the Services will be transferred to, processed and stored on our servers in the United States where the data protection laws may differ from those in your jurisdiction.

If we transfer your personal data out of the EEA to countries not deemed by the European Commission to provide an adequate level of personal data protection, we will ensure there are measures in place to safeguard your personal data. For further information on the mechanism(s) used to transfer your personal data, please contact us at Ronin@Roningallery.com.

##  **YOUR CHOICES**

###  **Unsubscribe from Emails**

Should you receive a promotional email or newsletter from us, you may opt out of receiving additional promotional email communications from us by following the unsubscribe instructions on the emails. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional communications from us, we may continue to send you non-promotional emails.

###  **Changing Account Settings**

You can access, update, or request deletion of your personal data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you. ****

###  **Opt Out of Tracking Technologies**

Regular cookies generally may be disabled or removed using tools available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some instances blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Browsers offer different functionalities and options so you may need to set them separately. Also, tools from commercial browsers may not be effective with regard to Flash cookies (also known as locally shared objects), HTML5 cookies or other tracking technologies. Please be aware if you disable or remove these technologies, some parts of the Service may not work and that when you revisit the Service, your ability to limit browser-based tracking technologies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.

Your browser settings may allow you to transmit a “Do Not Track” signal when you visit various websites. Like many websites, this Service is not designed to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from browsers. To learn more about “Do Not Track” signals, you may wish to visit <http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>.

###  **Opt Out of Analytics and Interest-Based Advertising**

You may [click here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) to learn more about Google Analytics. You may exercise choices regarding the use of cookies from Google Analytics by visiting <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> or downloading the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>.

You may learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting: <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>. To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada <http://youradchoices.ca/> or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

##  **EEA DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS**

The GDPR provides EEA data subjects with certain rights regarding their personal data. Subject to certain conditions, if you are an EEA data subject you may ask us to take the following actions in relation to the personal data that we hold about you:

  * Provide you with information about our processing of your personal data and give you access to your personal data.
  * Update or correct inaccuracies in your personal data.
  * Delete your personal data.
  * Object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes.
  * Object to reliance on our legitimate interests as the basis for processing of your personal data.
  * Restrict the processing of your personal data.
  * Transfer a machine-readable copy of your personal data to you or a third-party of your choice.

You can submit these requests by email to Ronin@Roningallery.com or to our postal address below. Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity prior to processing such requests. Applicable law may require or permit us to decline your request. If we decline your request, we will tell you why, subject to legal restrictions. If you would like to submit a complaint about our collection and use of your personal data or our response to your requests regarding your personal data,  you may contact us at [ronin@roningallery.com] or lodge a complaint with your supervisory authority.

##  **PAYMENTS**

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors), such as Authorize.net.

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal data is governed by their privacy policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

##  **LINKS TO OTHER SITES  **

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites. We strongly advise you to review the privacy policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.

##  **CHILDREN'S POLICY**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 16.

We do not intend to collect personal data  from anyone under the age of 16. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected personal data from your child without verification of parental consent, we will delete the information in accordance with applicable law.

##  **YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

California law permits customers in California to request certain details about how their “personal information” (as defined by California Civil Code Section 1798.83) is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. We do not share personal information with third parties or affiliates for those third parties’ or affiliates’ own direct marketing purposes. Californians may request information about our compliance with this law by contacting us at [ronin@roningallery.com] or by postal mail to:

Ronin Gallery LLC

Attention: California Privacy Rights Inquiry

425 Madison Avenue

New York, NY 10017

Your inquiry must specify “California Privacy Rights Request” in the subject line of the email or the first line of the letter, and include your name, street address, city, state and zip code. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per California resident a year.

##  **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will update the "Last Updated" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

##  **CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * By email: Ronin@RoninGallery.com
  * By phone number: 212-688-0188
  * By postal mail: Ronin Gallery LLC, 425 Madison Avenue, New York, NY 10017
